(Raj:)if you hadn't been
my role model.
(Raj:)Who wants to go to Vegas
in a real helicopter?!
(Leonard(on screen):)It was L. Frank Baum who said,
"No thief, however skillful,
can rob one of knowledge,
(Leonard(on screen):)and that is why knowledge is
the best and safest treasure."
(Leonard(on screen):)Wow, I'm boring myself.
(sighs)
(Leonard(on screen):)Sorry, I can't see
any of your faces right now,
(Leonard(on screen):)but I bet they look like this.
(Leonard(on screen):)Uh, you know,
I-I wrote an entire speech
(Leonard(on screen):)to say how high school
prepares you
(Leonard(on screen):)and what a wonderful
place it is,
(Leonard(on screen):)but I hated it.
(Leonard(on screen):)Maybe high school's great
if you look like this...
(Leonard(on screen):)...but I didn't even feel like
I existed at that school.